tutorialkit.com 2006-11-27

# Tutorial Kit Privacy Policy

TutorialKit.com (hereafter referred to as Company) has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users. 

What this Privacy Policy Covers

This privacy policy covers Company's treatment of personally identifiable information collected by Company through a website owned and operated by Company. 

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Company does not own or control, or of persons that Company does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Company's websites link. 

Collection and Use of Personal Information

You can visit the websites of Company without revealing any personal information. However, Company needs certain information if you wish to submit your tutorials, register for an author account, or use certain Company services. 

Where required, this information may include your personal contact information. Company will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with request services, to set up your member's account, and to contact you regarding new products and services. 

By accessing the services of Company and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with the privacy policy. 

Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

Company automatically receives and records non-personal information on over server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. Company may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your request for certain products and services. However, Company does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you. 

Company also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisement on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policy, and Company assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Company may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of Company to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information. 

Company may otherwise disclose you personal information when: 

\- We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose; 

\- We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process; 

\- We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of Company; 

\- We find that actions on our websites violate the Company Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

Consent

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in the policy, please do not provide any personal information to Company. If you have provided personal information to Company and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please contact us. 

Security

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, our Company Information protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, Company uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

We also safeguard your personal information from authorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures. 

Further, Company retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above or as required by law. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy

Company may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of Company websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof. 

Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please contact us.
